import pandas as pd
import numpy as np

# Calculate ADX(14) on H1 using available columns
# ADX = (TRIMA of +DI - TRIMA of -DI) / TRIMA of TR
# Since we don't have +DI/-DI, we approximate trend strength using ATR ratio or use a simplified proxy
# However, the prompt says "Use ATR instead of ADX" if concepts are missing.
# We will use a normalized ATR ratio on H1 as a proxy for trend strength (High ATR relative to price = strong trend)
#
